Guide to the New Yorkers at Work Oral History Collection OH.001
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
New Yorkers at Work Oral History Collection
1979-2000
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
Bernhardt, Debra E.
Baskin, Alex
Harris, Joseph
Kornblun, Joyce
Ramirez, Antonio
Weinstock, Louis, 1903-1994
OH.001
15 Linear Feet (approximately 300 cassette tapes)
New Yorkers at Work is an ongoing oral history project of New York University's Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives that seeks to document the history of labor and the working experiences of New Yorkers.
Access Restrictions
Some restrictions on access. For information contact: tamiment.wagner@nyu.edu.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
This collection was created by Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives with funding from the Rockefeller Foundation; additional materials were donated by Alex Baskin in 1997, Joseph Harris in 1991, Joyce Kornblun in 1982, Antonio Ramirez in 1996, and Louis Weinstock in 1981. The accession numbe associated with this collection is 1979.012.
Arrangement
The interviews are grouped into 1 series, arranged alphabetically by the name of the interviewee in finding aid. Access compact disks have been assigned numbers based on order of digitization.
Historical/Biographical Note
Begun in 1979, The New Yorkers at Work Oral History Collection is an ongoing series of interviews, conducted primarily by the staff of New York University's Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives, that document the history of labor in the metropolitan area. The largest group of interviews were collected for the New Yorkers at Work: Oral Histories of Life, Labor, and Industry Curriculum Project. In 1980, with a grant from the New York Council for the Humanities, about 150 interviews were conducted with workers and union activists in industries representative of the city's economy. Eight documentary radio programs were produced from these interviews for broadcast over National Public Radio. Additional interviews were conducted by Archive staff to augment archival and manuscript collections; a few others were donated by researchers or students. The most extensive of these was a series of 15 interviews conducted by SUNY Old Westbury Labor Studies students of Professor Joe Harris—many of them with Long Island labor leaders.
Scope and Content Note
The collection consists of oral history interviews broadly representative of 20th century New York City working conditions and union experiences. Topics include the impact of labor-saving construction techniques on the building trades; immigrant labor; CIO organization; the role of the Left in the labor movement and the impact of the expulsion of communist-dominated unions in 1949; public employee collective bargaining and the Fiscal Crisis of 1974-75; clerical organizing; new technology and its impact on printers and longshoremen; and the quest for economic opportunity by minorities and women. Please note the use of some interviews is restricted; transcripts or indexes exist for several of the tapes/CDs.
Notable interviewees include: Harry Avrutin, Brenda Berkman, Peter J. Brennan, Philip A. Carey, Charles Cogen, Edward J. Cleary, Sam Dolgoff, Ralph Fasanella, Abram Flaxer, Harry Fleischman, Philoine Fried, Dolores Huerta, Theodore Woodrow Kheel, Kitty Krupat, Josie McMillian, Joyce Miller, Pauline Newman, Lillian Roberts, Cleveland L. Robinson, Joe Stack, Leon Sverdlove, and Belle Zeller.
Labor unions and other organizations documented include: Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America; New York Joint Board; AFSCME; District Council 37 (New York, N.Y.); Bakery and Confectionery Workers' International Union of America; Coalition of Labor Union Women (U.S.); Communist Party of the United States of America; International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers; Local no. 3 (New York, N.Y.), International Jewelry Workers Union; International Ladies' Garmet Workers' Union; International Longshoremen's Association; National Maritime Union of America; New York Hotel Trades Council; Newspaper Guild of New York; Social Service Employees Union; Local 371 (New York, N.Y.); United Automobile; Aircraft, and Vehicle Workers of America; District 65; United Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers of America; United Farm Workers of America; United Federation of Teachers; United Office and Professional Workers of America; United Storeworkers (Organization); and Local 3 (New York, N.Y.).
Audiovisual Access Policies and Procedures
Access to audiovisual materials in this collection is available through digitized access copies. Researchers may view an item's original container, but the media themselves are not available for playback because of preservation concerns. Materials that have already been digitized are noted in the collection's finding aid and can be requested in our reading room. Materials not yet digitized will need to have access copies made before they can be used. To request an access copy, or if you are unsure if an item has been digitized, please contact tamiment.wagner@nyu.edu with the collection name, collection number, and a description of the item(s) requested. A staff member will respond to you with further information.
Labor unions -- Organizing -- United States.; Oral histories (literary works); Construction workers -- New York (State) -- New York -- Interviews; Labor unions -- New York (State) -- New York -- History -- 20th century.; Electric industry workers |z New York (State) |z New York |v Interviews.; Merchant mariners |z New York (State) |z New York |v Interviews.; Clerks |z New York (State) |z New York |v Interviews.; Hotels |x Employees |z New York (State) |z New York |v Interviews.; Clothing workers |z New York (State) |z New York |v Interviews.; Women employees |z New York (State) |z New York |v Interviews.; Municipal officials and employees |z New York (State) |z New York |v Interviews.; Stevedores -- New York (State) -- New York -- Interviews.; Working class |z New York (State) |z New York |v Interviews.; United Storeworkers (Organization). Local 3 (New York, N.Y.); International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union; Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America. New York Joint Board; Avrutin, Harry; Stack, Joe -- Interviews.; Sverdlove, Leon -- Interviews.; Robinson, Cleveland L. (Cleveland Lowellyn), 1914-1995; Miller, Joyce -- Interviews.; Newman, Pauline.; Huerta, Dolores, 1930-; Fried, Philoine; Cleary, Edward J. (Edward John), 1906-; Dolgoff, Sam, 1902-1990 -- Interviews; Carey, Philip A.; Cogen, Charles, 1903- -- Interviews; Zeller, Belle, 1903-; Brennan, Peter J., 1918-1996; Berkman, Brenda -- Interviews; Fleischman, Harry -- Interviews; Flaxer, Abram, 1904- -- Interviews; Kheel, Theodore Woodrow -- Interviews; Fasanella, Ralph -- Interviews; Krupat, Kitty; McMillian, Josie -- Interviews.; Roberts, Lillian; United Federation of Teachers; AFSCME. District Council 37 (New York, N.Y.); United Office and Professional Workers of America; International Longshoremen's Association; United Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers of America; United Farm Workers of America; International Union, United Automobile, Aerospace, and Agricultural Implement Workers of America. District 65; New York Hotel Trades Council; Social Service Employees Union. Local 371; Newspaper Guild of New York; National Maritime Union of America; International Jewelry Workers Union; Communist Party of the United States of America; International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers. Local 3 (New York, N.Y.); Bakery and Confectionery Workers International Union of America; Coalition of Labor Union Women (U.S.); Baskin, Alex; Harris, Joseph; Kornblun, Joyce; Ramirez, Antonio; Weinstock, Louis, 1903-1994
- Bernard and Marty Adelstein Description: Teamsters Local 813 and 1034, undated; cuid264; 182930 (Cd OH-01-001 / OH-01-002, Cassette 182A - 182B)
  General
  Transcript available Box 1
- Marge Albert Description: District 65, UAW; Clerical workers, organizing, 1970s, undated; 103918 (Cassette 1A - 1O)
  General note
  Index available
- Tony Alleyne Description: Taxi cab driver; Immigration, West Indian, Nov 21, 1981; 103917 (Cassette 2A, Cd OH-01-005)
  Index available; Transcript available Box 1
- Joseph Alissipi Description: Pennsylvania Mineworker, Apr 15, 1990; 103916 (Cassette 209A - 209C, Cd OH-01-431 / OH-01-432 / OH-01-433)
  Transcript available Box 1; Index available; Release form
- Kathy Andrade, Dec 11, 1998; 182997 (Cassette 251A - 251C)
- Sam Angel Description: Paperworkers Union, Local 107; Immigration, Sephardic Jewish, Jan 3, 1980; 103915 (Cd OH-01-196, Cassette 3A)
  Transcript available Box 1; Release form Yes
- Stanley Aslanian Description: NY Lithographers and Photographic Engraves Union, Local 1, Jul 11, 1984; 182932 (Cd OH-01-006, Cassette 137A)
- Sylvia & George Aronov Description: Socialist Party & Garment Work, Dec 12, 1995 - Dec 20, 1995; 103914 (Cd OH-01-197 / OH-01-198 / OH-01-199 / OH-01-200, Cd OH-01-201 / OH-01-202 / OH-01-203 / OH-01-204, Cd OH-01-205 / OH-01-206, Cassette 152A - 152E)
- Larry Atkins Description: BCT, Local 3, Jul 16, 1996; 103913 (Cassette 232A - 232B, Cd OH-01-207)
  Transcript available Box 1; Index available; Release form Yes
- William Atkinson Description: Department Store Workers, Local 1-S; Job discrimination, Jun 16, 1981; 103912 (Cassette 4A, Cd OH-01-007 / OH-01-008)
  Electronic Transcript and Index available
  Release form Yes
- Harry Avrutin Description: Bookkeepers, Stenographers and Accountants Union; Clerical workers organizing, 1930s, Jul 7, 1981; 103911 (Cassette 5A, Cd OH-01-009)
- Irving Axelrod Description: Painter, Sep 18, 1980; 103910 (Cassette 6A - 6B, Cd OH-01-011, Cd OH-01-010 / OH-01-011)
- Gilbert Banks Description: Harlem fight back; Job discrimination, minority construction, Oct 22, 1980; 103907 (Cassette 7A - 7B, Cd OH-01-210 / OH-01-211)
- Roger Baldwin Description: Clerical Worker, undated; 103908 (Cassette 156A - 156C, Cd OH-01-209)
  Electronic Transcript available
- Harry Belkin Description: Painter, Sep 18, 1980; 103906 (Cd OH-01-012 / OH-01-013, Cassette 8A - 8B)
- Jim Bell Description: District 65, United Auto Workers; Black Trade Unionist, undated; 103905 (Cassette 9A, Cd OH-01-014)
- Peter Bell Description: International Longshoremen's Association; Technology, Aug 29, 1981; 103904 (Cd OH-01-477 / OH-01-478, Cassette 10A - 10B)
- Ronald and Peter Bell Description: International Longshoremen's Association, Aug 29, 1981; 182949 (Cassette 11A - 11B, Cd OH-01-015 / OH-01-016)
- Jane Benedict Description: United Office Professional Workers; Clerical workers organizing 1930s, Dec 6, 1983; 103902 (Cd OH-01-372, Cassette 14A)
- Gloria Bendhurst Description: United Federation of Teachers, undated; 103903 (Cassette 12A, Cd OH-01-370 / OH-01-371)
- Julia Benicci Description: International Ladies Garment Workers; Immigration, Italian, Sep 20, 1981; 103901 (Cd OH-01-224 / OH-01-225, Cassette 13A)
- Robert Benson Description: IBEW, Local 1381, Apr 15, 1991; 182927 (Cd OH-01-017, Cassette 193A)
- Brenda Berkman Description: United Women Firefighters, Apr 4, 1993; Mar 1, 1995; 103900 (Cassette 214A - 214C, Cd OH-01-212 / OH-01-213 / OH-01-214)
  Transcript available Box 1; Release form
- Al Berknopf, May 6, 1980 - May 8, 1980; 460638
- Howard Bethel, Apr 14, 1978; 103897 (Box 1, Item Session: 137)
- Jack Bigel Description: Harry VanArsdale, Jul 30, 1987; 182933 (Cd OH-01-215)
- Ted Bleeker, Mar 6, 1996; 103896 (Cassette 154, Cd OH-01-352 / OH-01-353 / OH-01-354)
  Transcript available Box 1; Release form Y
- John Boer Description: AFSCME, District Council 37; Public employee collective bargaining, Feb 6, 1981; Mar 2, 1981; 103895 (Cd OH-01-216 / OH-01-217 / OH-01-218 / OH-01-219, Cd OH-01-220 / OH-01-221, Cassette 15A - 15C)
- Herbie Bostick Description: BCT, Local 3, Jul 16, 1996; 103894 (Cassette 234A - 234B, Cd OH-01-373 / OH-01-374)
- August Brand Description: Immigration, German; Furniture maker; Handwritten autobiography available, May 14, 1980; 103893 (Cassette 16A - 16B, Cd OH-01-023 / OH-01-024)
- Sara Bransford, Apr 12, 1990; 103892 (Cassette 180A - 180B, Cd OH-01-025 / OH-01-026 / OH-01-027)
- Peter Brennan, undated; 103891 (Cassette 194A MISSING)
  Electronic Transcript available; Release form Yes
- George Brooks, Apr 8, 1991; 182928 (Cd OH-01-028, Cassette 195A)
- May Brooks, Dec 13, 1994; 103890 (Box 1, Item Session: 225)
  Electronic Transcript available; Release form Yes*amended
- Thomas R. Brooks, 1991; 182929 (Cd OH-01-492 / OH-01-029 / OH-01-030, Cassette 210A - 210B)
  General Note
- Frank Brown Description: District 65, United Auto Workers, Nov 25, 1980; 103889 (Cd OH-01-222 / OH-01-223, Cassette 17A - 17B)
- Mollie Brown, Apr 3; 182996 (Cassette 189A)
  No Transcript
- Al Berknopf, May 6, 1980; Oct 8, 1980; 103899 (Cassette 157A - 157B, Cd OH-01-020 / OH-01-021 / OH-01-022)
- Armando Betanses Description: Hotel Trades Council, Local 6, Jul 23, 1996; 103898 (Cassette 233A - 233B, Cd OH-01-018 / OH-01-019)
- Bernard Cacchione Description: Social Service Employers Union; Collective bargaining, social workers, Jun 30, 1980; cuid265; 103887 (Cassette 18A, Cd: OH-01-834)
- Lonnie Cacchione Description: Social Service Employers Union; NYC Fiscal Crisis, 1975, undated; 103886 (Cd OH-01-233 / OH-01-234, Cassette 19A)
  Transcript available Box 2; Index available
- Angus Campbell Description: Seafarer's International Union, Jul 19, 1980; 103885 (Cd OH-01-031, Cassette 20A)
  Transcript available Box 2
- Anthony Caprano Description: Amalgamated Clothing Workers Union, Jun 11, 1981; 103884 (Cassette 144A, Cd OH-01-032)
  Transcript available Box 2; Release form Yes
- Joe Califf Description: CPUSA, Apr 24, 1994; 103883 (Cassette 219A - 219B, Cd OH-01-235 / OH-01-236)
- Father Philip Carey Description: Xavier School of Industrial Relations, Feb 19, 1981; 103882 (Cassette 21A - 21C, Cd OH-01-434-436)
  Index available; Release form Yes
- Elizabeth Smith Cassidy Description: Hotel and Restaurant Workers, Local 6, Dec 6, 1996; 103881 (Cassette 235A - 235B, Cd OH-01-033 / OH-01-034)
  Transcript available Box 2; Index available; Release form Yes
- Joseph E. Cavanagh Description: Commissioner of Labor, Suffolk County, NY, Dec 20, 1988; 103880 (Cassette 181A - 181B)
- Frank Cedarwall Description: IWW, undated; 182926 (Cassette 151A - 151B, Cd OH-01-035 / OH-01-036)
- May Chen, Apr 4, 2003; 182935 (Cassette 259A, Cd OH-01-237)
  Related Archival Materials
  Additional transcript of this interview can be found in the Asian Garment Workers in New York City Oral History Collection (OH 018).
- Sam Cimaglia Description: Cemetery Workers, Local 365, Nov 17, 1990; 103879 (Cassette 171A - 171B, Cd OH-01-037 / OH-01-038)
- George Cirkiel Description: United Auto Workers, District 65, May 20, 1980; 103878 (Cassette 22A, Cd OH-01-238)
- Ed Cleary Description: Building and Construction Trades Council, NYC; Job discriminaton, minorities, Oct 9, 1980; 103877 (Cassette 24A - 24B)
- Ed Cleary Sr. Description: International Brotherhood of Electrical Works. Local 3; Construction, NYC, 1920s-1950s, Nov 30, 1980; 103876 (Cassette 23A MISSING)
- Victor Clement Description: Brick layer; Construction industry, 1890-1950, Jul 3, 1980; 103875 (Cd OH-01-039 / OH-01-040, Cassette 25A - 25B)
- Cynthia Copeland Cochran, Jun 7, 1994; 103874 (Cd OH-01-241, Cassette 220A)
- Charles Cogen Description: United Federation of Teachers; Teacher's Guild, Oct 15, 1980; 103873 (Cassette 26A - 26B, Cd OH-01-239 / OH-01-240)
- Charles Everett Colcord Description: American Radio Association; Port Security Act, Nov 23, 1984; 103872 (Cassette 27A - 27B, Cd OH-01-041 / OH-01-042 / OH-01-043)
- Roger Cole Description: Civil Service Employee Association, undated; 103871 (Box 1, Item no tape)
- Mabel Collie, Oct 12, 1990; 103870 (Cd OH-01-044, Cassette 173A)
- Sharon Collie Description: Mt. Sinai nurse, Oct 24, 1990; 103869 (Cassette 172A)
- Mary Condon Description: Domestic Worker; Immigration, Ireland, Nov 2, 1980; 103868 (Cassette 28A, Cd OH-01-045 / OH-01-046)
- Simm Covington Description: NY Transit Authority, SSSA Union, undated; 182936 (Cassette 196A, Cd OH-01-242)
- Ed Cross Description: Tunnel Worker Local 147; Job discrimination, minorities, Mar 20, 1980; 103867 (Cassette 29A - 29B, Cd OH-01-047 / OH-01-048)
- George Culliman Description: National Maritime Union, Mar 26, 1981; 103866 (Cd OH-01-243 / OH-01-244 / OH-01-245 / OH-01-246 / OH-01-247 / OH-01-248, Cassette 30A - 30C)
- Bob Croghan, May 13 and May 20, 2004; 313015 (Dvd OH-01-489 / OH-01-490)
  Beta File; Access DVD
- Armand D'Angelo Description: Speaks about Harry van Arsdale, Jul 22, 1986; 103864 (Cassette 146A, Cd OH-01-436 / OH-01-437)
- Frank DaVito Description: United Food and Commerical Workers, Local 1245, Aug 28, 1989; 182924 (Cassette 166A, Cd OH-01-049)
- Louis D'Incecco, undated; 182937 (Cassette 183A, Cd OH-01-249)
- Domenic DiPaola Description: Pocketbook Worker, Organization: Local 1, Jan 13, 1994; 103863 (Cd OH-01-050 / OH-01-051, Cassette 218A - 218B)
- Robert Dobbs, undated; 103862 (Cassette 246A)
- Herbert Dohms, Jun 2, 1990; 103861 (Cd OH-01-052, Cassette 167A)
- Esther Dolgoff, Apr 17, 1979; 182925 (Cassette 186A, Cd OH-01-053)
- Sam Dolgoff Description: Immigration, Eastern European Jewish; Anarchism, Jul 21, 1981; 103860 (Cassette 31A, Cd OH-01-054 / OH-01-055)
- Julius Drumright Description: Tunnel Workers, Local 147; Job discrimination, minorities, Jul 23, 1977; 103859 (Cd OH-01-056, Cassette 32A)
  Index available; Release form yes
- Johnnie Dwyer Description: International Brotherhood of Longshoremen; flie includes many clippings, Nov 21, 1980; 103858 (Cd OH-01-057 / OH-01-058, Cassette 34A - 34B)
  Electronic Transcript available; Release form
- Jeff Eichler Description: United Staff Association of NYU, Local 3882 AFT; clerical and secretarial worker organizing, 1979-1980s, Mar 8, 1994; 103856 (Cassette 225A - 225B, Cd OH-01-250 / OH-01-251)
- Emmanuel Eisenhandler, undated; 182995 (Cassette 184A)
- Hilliard Ellis African-American trade unionism; UAW/Transport Workers, 1981; 103855 (Cd OH-01-252 / OH-01-253, Cassette 35A)
- Ralph Fasenella Description: United Electrical Workers; McCarthyism, Apr 6, 1981; 103853 (Cassette 36A, Cd OH-01-059 / OH-01-060)
- Charles Fay Description: United Electrical Workers, Local 475, Apr 10, 1986; 103852 (Cd OH-01-061 / OH-01-062, Cassette 37A - 37B)
- Al Filardo Description: Carpenter; Construction industry, NYC, 1950s-1960s, Oct 10, 1986; 103851 (Cd OH-01-063 / OH-01-064, Cassette 38A - 38B)
- Ann Filardo, undated; 239181 (Cassette 197A-B, Cd OH-01-438 / OH-01-439 / OH-01-440)
- Jack Finn Description: National Maritime Union, Jul 22, 1981; 103850 (Cd OH-01-367 / OH-01-368 / OH-01-369, Cassette 39A - 39C)
- Father Joseph Fitzpatrick Description: Fordham University, Oct 12, 1990; 103849 (Cassette 169A - 169D)
- Abe Flaxer Description: United Public Workers; McCarthyism, Apr 7, 1981; Apr 23, 1981; May 18, 1981; 103848 (Cassette 40A - 40D, Cd OH-01-485 / OH-01-486)
- Harry Fleischman Description: Socialist Party, Jun 8, 1981; Jun 15, 1981; Jun 22, 1981; 103846 (Cassette 41A - 41D, Cd OH-01-254 / OH-01-255 / OH-01-256 / OH-01-257 / OH-01-258 / OH-01-259)
- Henry Foner, Nov 21, 2002; 182938 (Cd OH-01-260 / OH-01-261, Cassette 247A)
  Transcript available Box 3; Release form Yes
- Henry Foner and Charles Klare, Jul 20, 1998; 182939 (Cd OH-01-262 / OH-01-263)
  Transcript available Box 3
- Maurice Fredericks Description: Brooklyn, CORE; Job discrimination, Apr 28, 1981; Jul 3, 1981; 103845 (Cassette 42A - 42D, Cd OH-01-441 / OH-01-442 / OH-01-443)
  Release form
- Daniel P. French, Oct 23, 1992; 103844 (Cassette 213A, Cd OH-01-065)
- Sam Friedman Description: Socialist Party, Feb 19, 1986; Jan 21, 1990; 103842 (Cassette 165A, Cd OH-01-465, Cassette 43A - 43F)
- Allen Ernestine Description: Negro Actor's Guild, Feb 4, 1985; 182931 (Cd OH-01-003 / OH-01-004, Cassette 162A - 162B)
- Philoene Fried, daughter of Sidney Hillman, Jan 12, 1988; 103843 (Cassette 150A - 150B, Cd OH-01-066, Cd OH-01-067)
  Transcript available Box 4; Release form Yes
- Jimi Gavin National Maritime Union, Aug 26, 1986; Aug 29, 1986; 103840 (Cassette 163A - 163F, Cd OH-01-068 / OH-01-069 / OH-01-070 / OH-01-071 / OH-01-072, Cd OH-01-073 / OH-01-074 / OH-01-075 / OH-01-076 / OH-01-077 / OH-01-078)
- James Garry, Mar 21, 1989; 182994 (Cassette 221A)
- Bessie Geller, Jun 29, 1991; 103839 (Cassette 191A MISSING)
- Irving Genn, Mar 29, 1990; 103838 (Cassette 164A - 164B, Cd OH-01-079 / OH-01-080)
- Laviere (Larry) Gentile Description: Hotel, Restaurant & Club Employees and Bartenders, Local 6, Sep 19, 1996; 103837 (Cd OH-01-081 / OH-01-082, Cassette 237A - 237B)
- Miriam Gittelson, Jun 3, 1999; 103836 (Cd OH-01-083 / OH-01-084, Cassette 255A - 255B)
- John Glasel, Jun 2, 1993; 103835 (Cassette 215A - 215B)
- Thomas Gleason Description: International Longshoremen's Association, Jul 31, 1980; 103834 (Cassette 44A, Cd OH-01-085)
- Max Goodheim Description: Immigration, Poland; Pocketbook maker, Jun 30, 1981; Sep 21, 1981; 103833 (Cassette 45A - 45C, Cd OH-01-264 / OH-01-265 / OH-01-266 / OH-01-267 / OH-01-268)
  Transcript available Box 3; Index available
- Michael Goodwin Description: AFL-CIO, May 28, 1999; 103832 (Cassette 252A, Cd OH-01-086)
- Lou Gordon Description: Paperworkers, Local 107, Sep 10, 1979; 103831 (Cd OH-01-269 / OH-01-270 / OH-01-271 / OH-01-272, Cassette 46A - 46B)
- Joseph Gould, Dec 2, 1989; 103830 (Cassette 158A - 158B, Cd OH-01-087 / OH-01-088)
- Paul Green, Sep 25, 1992; 103829 (Cassette 212A - 212B, Cd OH-01-273 / OH-01-274 / OH-01-275)
- Florence Grogan, Oct 25, 1996; 103828 (Cd OH-01-466 / OH-01-467, Cassette 236A)
  Transcript available Box 3; Index available; Release form Yes
- Paul Hall Description: Seafarers International Union, 1969; 103826 (Cd OH-01-491, Cassette 47A)
- Helmut A. Hallex Description: Immigration, Germany, Mar 8, 1980; Mar 22, 1980; 103825 (Cassette 48A - 48D, Cd OH-01-276 / OH-01-277 / OH-01-278 / OH-01-279 / OH-01-280 / OH-01-281)
- James Haughton Description: Harlem Fight Back; Job discrimination, minorities, Oct 22, 1980; 103824 (Cassette 49A - 49B, Cd OH-01-089 / OH-01-090)
- Peter Hawley Description: United Office & Professional Workers; clerical worker organizing, Dec 6, 1983; 103823 (Cd OH-01-392 / OH-01-393 / OH-01-394, Cassette 50A - 50B)
- Charles Hayes Description: Black Trade Unionist, Jul 23, 1981; 103822 (Cd OH-01-386, Cassette 51A)
- Stan Hill Description: AFSCME, District Council 37, Sep 6, 1982; 103821 (Cd OH-01-322, Cassette 52A)
- Harold Hoffman, Feb 14, 1985; 182993 (Cd OH-01-468, Cassette 161A)
- Walter Hooke, Jul 16, 1994; 103819 (Cassette 223A - 223D, Cd OH-01-375 / OH-01-376 / OH-01-377 / OH-01-378)
- Ben Holzman Description: Furniture Workers; Immigration, Poland, May 17, 1981; 103820 (Cassette 53A MISSING)
- Dolores Huerta Description: United Farm Workers, Sep 4, 1986; 103818 (Cd OH-01-091, Cassette 54A)
- Sidney Jonas Description: Shoe Workers Union; Communist Party Opposition (Lovestonites), Dec 12, 1982; Sep 12, 1983; Sep 3, 1983; 103816 (Cassette 55A - 55D, Cd OH-01-357 / OH-01-358 / OH-01-359 / OH-01-360)
- Julie Description: Clerical Worker, Nov 15, 1980; 103815 (Cassette 56A, Cd OH-01-479)
- Joe Kanowe, undated; 182940 (Cd OH-01-284 / OH-01-285, Cd OH-01-285)
- Edna Kaplan, undated; 103814 (Cassette 218.5 MISSING)
  Transcript available
- Harry Kelber Description: International Typographical Union; technology, Jun 19, 1980; 103813 (Cassette 57A, Cd OH-01-469: OH-01-475)
- Ruth Kessler Taylor Description: United Auto Workers, District 65; Housing integration in Stuy Town, NYC 1940s, undated; 182941 (Cd OH-01-444 / OH-01-445 / OH-01-446 / OH-01-447 / OH-01-448 / OH-01-449, Cassette 121A-C)
  Transcript available Box 5; Release form Yes
- Theodore Kheel Description: Labor negotiator, undated; 103812 (Cassette 58A, Cd OH-01-400)